{
	"title": "italiano",
	"cards": [
		{
			"front": "a buon mercato",
			"back": "cheap; at a good price"
		},
		{
			"front": "a destra",
			"back": "to the right"
		},
		{
			"front": "a presto!",
			"back": "see you soon!"
		},
		{
			"front": "a sinistra",
			"back": "to the left"
		},
		{
			"front": "abbastanza",
			"back": "enough"
		},
		{
			"front": "abitare",
			"back": "to live (somewhere); to reside"
		},
		{
			"front": "accendere",
			"back": "to ignite, to turn on"
		},
		{
			"front": "accettare",
			"back": "to accept; to admit"
		},
		{
			"front": "adesso",
			"back": "now"
		},
		{
			"front": "affaticato",
			"back": "tired"
		}
	]
}
